National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Records
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Case Files, 1988-2006, Undated; nam_apap298-1; 12.55 cubic ft.
  - Innocence, 1998-2000, Undated; nam_apap298-1.3; 0.58 cubic ft.
    - Green, Joseph (FL), 2000; nam_apap298-1.3_21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Guerra, Ricardo (TX), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_22 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Harris, Johnny (AL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_23 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Hauptmann, Richard (NJ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_24 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Hernandez, Alejandro (IL), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_25 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Herrera, Leonel (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_26 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Jacobs, Sonia (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_27 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Johnson, Edward (MS), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_28 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Johnson, Sammuel (MS), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_29 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Jones, Ronald (IL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_30 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Kyles, Curtis (LA), 1998; 2000; nam_apap298-1.3_31 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Landano, James (NJ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_32 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Lawson, Carl (IL), 2000; nam_apap298-1.3_33 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Macias, Federico (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_34 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Manning, Steven (IL), 2000; nam_apap298-1.3_35 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Marsh, Guy (MD), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_36 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Martinez, Daniel (NM), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_37 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - McMillian, Walter (AL), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_38 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Miranda, Roberto (NV), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_39 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Monroe, Donald (LA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_40 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Porter, Anthony (IL), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_41 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Pitts, Freddie/ Lee, Wilbert (FL), 1998; 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_42 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Ramos, Juan (FL), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_43 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Richardson, James (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_44 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Schlup, Lloyd (MD), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_45 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Scott, Brandley (FL), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_46 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Skelton, John (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_47 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Clarence (NM), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_48 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Jay (PA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_49 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Steven (IL), 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_50 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Sutton, Josiah (TX), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_51 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Tillis, Darby (IL), 2000; nam_apap298-1.3_52 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Vasquez, Dave (VA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_53 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Wallace, Robert (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_54 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Walker, Nathaniel (NJ), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_55 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Whitmore, George (NY), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_56 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Wilhoit, Gregory (OK), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_57 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Williams, Dennis (IL), 2000; nam_apap298-1.3_58 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Williams, Wayne (GA), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_59 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Zimmerman, Isidore (NY), Undated; nam_apap298-1.3_60 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Publications, 1982-2004, Undated; nam_apap298-2; 1 cubic ft.
  Alphabetical by subject
  Contains publications of national magazines, LifeLines, the official newsletters of the NCADP as well as publications by affiliate organizations.
  - Death Penalty Press, with inmate publication, 1988; nam_apap298-2_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Death Penalty Press, 1995 January-1998 October; nam_apap298-2_2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Death Penalty Press, 1999 January2000 April; nam_apap298-2_3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Death Penalty Press, 2001; nam_apap298-2_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Death Penalty Press, 2001; nam_apap298-2_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Death Penalty Press, Juveniles, Undated; nam_apap298-2_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising, 2004 May-2004 December; nam_apap298-2_7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lifelines 1-10, 1982 Spring-1984 March; nam_apap298-2_8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lifelines 11-20, 1984 April-1985 March; nam_apap298-2_9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lifelines 21-30, 1985 April-1986 October; nam_apap298-2_10 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Lifelines 31-40, 1986 November-1988 June; nam_apap298-2_11 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Lifelines 41-50, 1988 July-1990 October; nam_apap298-2_12 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Lifelines 51-60, 1991 January-1993 April; nam_apap298-2_13 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Lifelines 61-70, 1993 July-1997 September; nam_apap298-2_14 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Lifelines 71-80, 1997 November-1999 April; nam_apap298-2_15 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Lifelines 83-90, 2000; nam_apap298-2_16 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Lifelines 91-93, 2003; nam_apap298-2_17 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - National Execution Alert, 1994; nam_apap298-2_18 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - National Execution Alert, 1999; nam_apap298-2_19 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - National Execution Alert, 2000; nam_apap298-2_20 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Partisan Defense Committee, 2001; nam_apap298-2_21 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Subject Files, 1972-2005, Undated; nam_apap298-3; 5 cubic ft.
  This series includes reference material on death penalty law in both the United States and abroad. Items in this series relate to some aspect of the death penalty and focus on education. Subjects include juvenile executions, the cost of the death penalty, and its impact on victim and inmate families. Material consists of news articles, correspondence, newspaper clippings, press releases, statements, and reports.
  - Advocacy, 1983; nam_apap298-3_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abolition Movement, 1986; nam_apap298-3_2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Affiliate Packet, Undated; nam_apap298-3_3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alabama, 1990; nam_apap298-3_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alternatives, 1993 April; nam_apap298-3_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Baptist Churches, 1983 October; nam_apap298-3_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ACLU, 1984 June; nam_apap298-3_7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Ethical Union, 1988 April-1993 September; nam_apap298-3_8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1981 January; nam_apap298-3_9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Jewish Congress, 1983 October; nam_apap298-3_10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Orthopsychiatry Association, 1984 May; nam_apap298-3_11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Amnesty International, 1994 January; nam_apap298-3_12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Arguments, 1987; nam_apap298-3_13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Arkansas, 1994; nam_apap298-3_14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Arizona, 1990; nam_apap298-3_15 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Banner - 'National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, Undated; nam_apap298-3_16 (Oversized 1)
  - Bibliography of Publications by Subject [1 of 2], ca. 2001; nam_apap298-3_17 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bibliography of Publications by Subject [2 of 2], ca. 2001; nam_apap298-3_18 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bush, George W., 1997 November; nam_apap298-3_19 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - California, 1994; nam_apap298-3_20 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Canada Reinstatement Effort, 1987; nam_apap298-3_21 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Cartoons, 1988; nam_apap298-3_22 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Catholic Worker House, 1988 December-1994 February; nam_apap298-3_23 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Celebrities, 1993; nam_apap298-3_24 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights, 1981 October 1992; nam_apap298-3_25 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Christian Church, 1989 November; nam_apap298-3_26 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Church of the Brethren, 1984 January-1994 October; nam_apap298-3_27 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cure, 1986 February-1995 July; nam_apap298-3_28 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Citizens for Law and Order, 1991 February; nam_apap298-3_29 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Clemency, 1993 October-1999 June; nam_apap298-3_30 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Clippings - Bizarre, Undated; nam_apap298-3_31 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Clippings, 1987; nam_apap298-3_32 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Clippings, 1990; nam_apap298-3_33 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Clippings, 1992; nam_apap298-3_34 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Clippings, 1993; nam_apap298-3_35 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Clippings, 1994; nam_apap298-3_36 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Clippings, 1995; nam_apap298-3_37 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Clippings, 1996; nam_apap298-3_38 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Clippings, 1999; nam_apap298-3_39 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Colorado, 2005; nam_apap298-3_40 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Celeste Commutations, 1991; nam_apap298-3_41 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Commutations Post-Furman, 1999 May; nam_apap298-3_42 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Connecticut, 1995; nam_apap298-3_43 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Consensual Executions/Suicide, 1989; nam_apap298-3_44 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cost, Undated; nam_apap298-3_45 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cost, Undated; nam_apap298-3_46 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cost By State, 1982 April-1998 December; nam_apap298-3_47 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Cost Study By General Accounting Office, 1989 September; nam_apap298-3_48 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Criminal Justice Issues, Undated; nam_apap298-3_49 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Data CD - WDI 2003, nam_apap298-3_50 (Cd-r 1)
  - Death Penalty Information Center, 2002 October; nam_apap298-3_51 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Defense for Children International -USA, 1985 September-1992 April; nam_apap298-3_52 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Delaware, 2005; nam_apap298-3_53 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Delegation of Cuba, 2003 March; nam_apap298-3_54 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Diminished Capacity, 2002 June; nam_apap298-3_55 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Discrimination, 1991 June-2002 December; nam_apap298-3_56 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Discrimination, 1991 June-2002 December; nam_apap298-3_57 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Discrimination, 1991 June-2002 December; nam_apap298-3_58 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Education, 1988; nam_apap298-3_59 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Electrocution Packet, 1990 July; nam_apap298-3_60 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Episcopal Church, 1993 February; nam_apap298-3_61 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - European Parliament Meeting, 1988 June; nam_apap298-3_62 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Evangelical Lutheran Church, 1984 March-1995 April; nam_apap298-3_63 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Executions 100th, 1988; nam_apap298-3_64 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Executions 200th, 1992; nam_apap298-3_65 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Executions, 2001; nam_apap298-3_66 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Exonerations, Undated; nam_apap298-3_67 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Facts and FAQ'S, 1995 January; nam_apap298-3_68 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Experts/Authorities, 1989 June; nam_apap298-3_69 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Faith Based Organizations, Undated; nam_apap298-3_70 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Families: Inmates, 1982 September; nam_apap298-3_71 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Families: Victims, 1981 September; nam_apap298-3_72 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Families: Victims Services, 1984 September; nam_apap298-3_73 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Federal, 1989; 2000; Undated; nam_apap298-3_74 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Federal Crime Bill, 1988; nam_apap298-3_75 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Federal Crime Bill, 1989; nam_apap298-3_76 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Federal Crime Bill, 1990; nam_apap298-3_77 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Federal Crime Bill, 1991; nam_apap298-3_78 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Federal Crime Bill, 1993; nam_apap298-3_79 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Federal Crime Bill, 1993; nam_apap298-3_80 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 1987 March; nam_apap298-3_81 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Feminists For Life, 1992 October; nam_apap298-3_82 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Florida, 1990; nam_apap298-3_83 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Florida, 1995; nam_apap298-3_84 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Nationals, 1994; nam_apap298-3_85 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Furman v. Georgia, 1972; nam_apap298-3_86 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - GLBT Groups, 1999 February; nam_apap298-3_87 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Georgia, 1995; 1996; nam_apap298-3_88 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Georgia, 2005; nam_apap298-3_89 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Grigson - Dr. James, 2004 December; nam_apap298-3_90 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Idaho, 2005; nam_apap298-3_91 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Indiana, 1989; 1994; nam_apap298-3_92 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Innocence, 1985 November; nam_apap298-3_93 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - International Countries, 1994; nam_apap298-3_94 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - International Declaration of Life, 1994; nam_apap298-3_95 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - International Information, 2001; nam_apap298-3_96 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - International Soering Case, 1989 July; nam_apap298-3_97 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - International Standards, 1987; nam_apap298-3_98 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - International Law, 2004; nam_apap298-3_99 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - International - South Africa, 1996; nam_apap298-3_100 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Juvenile Campaign, Undated; nam_apap298-3_101 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Juvenile Campaign, Undated; nam_apap298-3_102 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Juvenile Campaign, Undated; nam_apap298-3_103 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Juvenile Campaign, Undated; nam_apap298-3_104 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Juvenile Campaign, Undated; nam_apap298-3_105 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Juvenile Campaign - Delaware, 2002; nam_apap298-3_106 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Juvenile Campaign - Delaware, 2002; nam_apap298-3_107 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Juvenile Campaign - Delaware, 2002; nam_apap298-3_108 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Juvenile Campaign - Delaware, 2002; nam_apap298-3_109 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Juvenile Campaign - Medical Research, 1986; nam_apap298-3_110 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Juvenile Death Penalty Today, 1985; nam_apap298-3_111 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Juvenile Death Penalty Today, 2000; nam_apap298-3_112 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Juvenile Justice, 2002 October; nam_apap298-3_113 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Juveniles - Arkansas, 2002 November-2003 March; nam_apap298-3_114 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Juveniles -General, 2005 October; nam_apap298-3_115 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Juveniles -General, 2005 October; nam_apap298-3_116 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Juveniles - Idaho, 2003 November-2004 March; nam_apap298-3_117 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Juveniles - New Hampshire, 2004 March; nam_apap298-3_118 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Juveniles - Sentencing, 1999 January; nam_apap298-3_119 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Juveniles - South Dakota [1 of 2], 2003 February; nam_apap298-3_120 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Juveniles - South Dakota [2 of 2], 2003 February; nam_apap298-3_121 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Juveniles - State Age Requirements, 1999 July; nam_apap298-3_122 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Juveniles - Transfers, 1996; nam_apap298-3_123 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Juveniles - Utah, 2002 November-2003 March; nam_apap298-3_124 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Kansas, 2005; nam_apap298-3_125 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Kentucky, 2005; nam_apap298-3_126 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Law Enforcement, 1989 September; nam_apap298-3_127 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Lawyers, 1990 December; nam_apap298-3_128 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 2005 January; nam_apap298-3_129 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Legislation, 1986; nam_apap298-3_130 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Legislation, 1993; nam_apap298-3_131 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Lethal Injection [1 of 2], 2001 September; nam_apap298-3_132 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Lethal Injection [2 of 2], 2001 September; nam_apap298-3_133 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Lobbying Information, Undated; nam_apap298-3_134 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Louisiana, 1995; Undated; nam_apap298-3_135 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Louisiana, 2005; nam_apap298-3_136 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Maryland, 1993; nam_apap298-3_137 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Maryland, 1997; nam_apap298-3_138 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Massachusetts, 1995; nam_apap298-3_139 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Medical Issues [1 of 5], 1990; 1994; 1996; Undated; nam_apap298-3_140 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Medical Issues [2 of 5], 1994; Undated; nam_apap298-3_141 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Medical Issues [3 of 5], 1987; 1989; 1990; 1993; Undated; nam_apap298-3_142 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Medical Issues [4 of 5], 1999; 2001; Undated; nam_apap298-3_143 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Medical Issues [5 of 5], 1999; Undated; nam_apap298-3_144 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Mental Retardation, 2002 February; nam_apap298-3_145 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Military, 1983; 1988; 1990; 1991; 1994; nam_apap298-3_146 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Mississippi, 1991; 1996; nam_apap298-3_147 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Mississippi, 2005; nam_apap298-3_148 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Missouri, 2005; nam_apap298-3_149 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Montana, 2005; nam_apap298-3_150 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Moratorium in (IL), 2000 April; nam_apap298-3_151 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Moratorium in (OK), 2001 January; nam_apap298-3_152 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - NCADP Press Packet, 1992; nam_apap298-3_153 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - NCADP Program/ Development, 2000; nam_apap298-3_154 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - NCADP Media/ Communication Committee, 2000 July; nam_apap298-3_155 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - National Committee, 1978 May-1990 June; nam_apap298-3_156 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Native American, 1992 November; nam_apap298-3_157 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Native Americans, 2002 January; nam_apap298-3_158 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Nebraska, 1995; nam_apap298-3_159 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Nebraska, 2005; nam_apap298-3_160 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Nevada, 2005; nam_apap298-3_161 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - New Mexico, 2005; nam_apap298-3_162 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - New York, 2005; nam_apap298-3_163 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Ohio, 1990; 1994; 1995; nam_apap298-3_164 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Oklahoma, 1990; nam_apap298-3_165 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Oklahoma, 2005; nam_apap298-3_166 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - OP - ED Press, 1987; nam_apap298-3_167 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - OP - ED Press, 1989; nam_apap298-3_168 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - OP - ED Press, 1990; nam_apap298-3_169 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - OP - ED Press, 1991; nam_apap298-3_170 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - OP - ED Press, 1992; nam_apap298-3_171 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - OP - ED Press, 1993; nam_apap298-3_172 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - OP - ED Press, 1994; nam_apap298-3_173 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Oregon, 2005; nam_apap298-3_174 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Oregon, Undated; nam_apap298-3_175 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Organizational History of the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, Undated; nam_apap298-3_176 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Papal Visit, 1987 January; nam_apap298-3_177 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Pennsylvania, 1994; 1995; 1997; nam_apap298-3_178 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania, 2005; nam_apap298-3_179 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - People Against Executions, 1979 June; nam_apap298-3_180 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Pharmaceutical Company Web Pages, 2001; nam_apap298-3_181 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Pharmaceutical Information, 2000; nam_apap298-3_182 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Photographic Documentation, 1992; nam_apap298-3_183 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Physicians and the Death Penalty, 2001; nam_apap298-3_184 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Pins, Texas Journey of Hope, Execution is Not the Solution, Execute Justice not People, 1988; Undated; nam_apap298-3_185 (Oversized 1)
  - Pro-Death Penalty, 1987; nam_apap298-3_186 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Proponent Writings & Statements, 1989; nam_apap298-3_187 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Prison Issues, 1997 October; nam_apap298-3_188 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Private Prisons, 2001 October; nam_apap298-3_189 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Public Opinion, 1989 February; nam_apap298-3_190 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Public Opinion By State, 1991 April-1994 October; nam_apap298-3_191 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Public Opinion By State, 1991 April-1994 October; nam_apap298-3_192 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Racial Justice Act, 1990 July; nam_apap298-3_193 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Religious, 1988; nam_apap298-3_194 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Religious, 1988; nam_apap298-3_195 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Report to the Executive Committee of the NCADP, 1981; nam_apap298-3_196 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - S. 2869, 2002 July; nam_apap298-3_197 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - South Carolina, 2005; nam_apap298-3_198 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - South Dakota, 1994; nam_apap298-3_199 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - South Dakota, 2005; nam_apap298-3_200 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - St. Louis County Minority Clerkship Program, 1999; nam_apap298-3_201 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Statements and Quotes, 1981 September; nam_apap298-3_202 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Stop Killing Kids Campaign, 1996 July; nam_apap298-3_203 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Supreme Court Justice Brennan, 1994 April; nam_apap298-3_204 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Supreme Court Justice Blackmun, 1994 February; nam_apap298-3_205 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Supreme Court Justice Ginsburg, 1993 June; nam_apap298-3_206 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Supreme Court Justice Kennedy, 1991 November; nam_apap298-3_207 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Supreme Court Justice Marshall, 1991 July; nam_apap298-3_208 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Supreme Court Justice Powell, 1988 August; nam_apap298-3_209 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Television Executions, 1991 May-1994 February; nam_apap298-3_210 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Tennessee, 1995; nam_apap298-3_211 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Texas, 2005; nam_apap298-3_212 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Texas, 1994; 1995; 1997; nam_apap298-3_213 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Texas, Undated; nam_apap298-3_214 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - United Nations Commission on Human Rights, 2002; nam_apap298-3_215 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - U.S Governors, 1999; nam_apap298-3_216 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Utah, 2005; nam_apap298-3_217 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Virginia, 2005; nam_apap298-3_218 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Women on Death Row, 1998 October; nam_apap298-3_219 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Workshop Survey - Presenters, Undated; nam_apap298-3_220 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Wyoming, 2004; nam_apap298-3_221 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Wyoming, 2005; nam_apap298-3_222 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Conferences, 1981-2005, Undated; nam_apap298-4; 0.55 cubic ft.
  Since 1981 the NCADP has held an annual national conference. Files in this series contain flyers, published materials, and documents from each conference. Also included is material from conferences held by affiliate organizations.
  - The Council of Europe, 2003; nam_apap298-4_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Death Penalty Abolition Institute, 2003; nam_apap298-4_2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Death Penalty Awareness Day, 1987; nam_apap298-4_3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Death Penalty Forum, 2004; nam_apap298-4_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - International Human Rights Conference [1 of 2], 2005; nam_apap298-4_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - International Human Rights Conference [2 of 2], 2005; nam_apap298-4_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - National Conference (Photographs), 1997; nam_apap298-4_7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - National Conference - Chicago, IL, 2002; nam_apap298-4_8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - National Conference - Little Rock, AR (Photographs), Undated; nam_apap298-4_9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - National Conference - Nashville, TN, 2003; nam_apap298-4_10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - National Conference - New Orleans, LA (Photographs, Undated; nam_apap298-4_11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - National Conference - Philadelphia, PA (with photographs), 1999; nam_apap298-4_12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - National Conference - Raleigh, NC, 2001; nam_apap298-4_13 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - National Conference - Seattle, WA (Photographs), Undated; nam_apap298-4_14 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - National Conference - St. Louis, MO (with photographs), 1998; nam_apap298-4_15 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - National Conference - Washington, DC, 1981; nam_apap298-4_16 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - National Conference - Washington, DC, 2004; nam_apap298-4_17 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Northeast Regional Conference - New Haven, CT, 1988; nam_apap298-4_18 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Student Death Penalty Conference, 2003; nam_apap298-4_19 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Wrongful Convictions Conference, 1999; nam_apap298-4_20 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Petitions, 1999; nam_apap298-5; 0.75 cubic ft.
  Alphabetical
  Contains the Stop Killing Kids Petitions with signatures gathered from the United States, Canada, and Europe.
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Belgium, Canada, United States [1 of 4], 1999; nam_apap298-5_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stop Killing Kids Petition Binder - Belgium, Canada, United States [2 of 4], 1999; nam_apap298-5_2 (Box 1, Folder 2)